Is it a little difficult here?
Ladies and gentlemen, the bathing scene.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
What?
What? The big problem's gone.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
She started crying.
I started to cry
Ryo-chan is doing her best
You're so good at that!
You did it!
Put it on tight!
It's going to work.
Wait, it's on.
Is it on?
It's on.
It's on!
It's on! I'm so happy!
Can I pull up the kelp now?
You can pull up the kelp now.
You can leave it in without pulling it up.
I see.
I don't know, but I'll put it in.
Choo-choo-choo!
You know, I'm going to use shiitake mushrooms to give it a little visual.
You know, for a visual.
Yeah.
Now we're in our leisure time.
Let's talk about the old days.
An old story.
Can we go over there?
Yeah. - Okay.
It's cold.
Let's eat while the rice cooks.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Well, it's good, then.
This is it, guys.
It's just the way we are.
Naochan is always like this.
Our legs overlap like this.
They're on top of each other.
Always.
Isn't she cute?
You're not cute.
You guys must be so jealous of me.
I'm not cute at all... and now I've been made public.
Can I open one?
Okay.
Hot, hot, hot.
Careful, careful, careful, careful.
Gung, gung, gung.
Wait, it's burning.
It's burning.
Oh, my God.
Roast! Roast! This is burnt rice!
The middle, oh, you shouldn't write that part down, either.
Try it. Chewing state.
It's weird. What?
Delicious! What?
It's so delicious!
Okoge is so delicious!
It's a rice cracker!
This is definitely rice cracker!
Wouldn't this be a real rice cracker if you poured soy sauce on it?
I'm sure.
Oh, the middle part is so good, for sure!
Nice okoge!
Here is the rice cracker!
It's ready!
Ta-da!
Insert
So, it's done, right?
It's done!
Okay, then, Yochanan, you're right, open it up.
Here we go!
Open!
Wow!
What?
Isn't it good?
Looks good!
Looks good, doesn't it?
It looks so good.
I made a pot.
Bon appétit!
Yes! No!
Okay, I'll get it over here. Take it.
What would you like to put in it?
Anything but mushrooms.
Oh, it looks so delicious!
I don't think I've ever eaten on this hearth before.
I'm so excited.
Bon appétit!
Okay. Yaah!
Bon appétit.
Oh, the pears are good.
Yeah, I want to put ponzu (Japanese citrus juice) in it.
Let's add some Chichibu no Shizuku.
Well, excuse me.
Spank. Here you go.
Anga-tsu.
Mmm! Yum! Delicious!
Mmm! Yum!
What does that taste like?
Oh, it smells so much like yuzu.
It's a yuzu foundation.
Wow.
Is it hot? Is it bad?
I thought I was gonna die.
So can I go with this shiitake mushroom?
Yes, you can.
Is it bad?
Nice and crunchy.
Yummy.
I don't know how good it tastes, but it looks good.
It's delicious.
I'll have some rice, too.
Eat up
Our blood, our tears, our sweat, our eraser stains.
Because there's no blood in it
Sweat and tears.
There's no blood in it.
Wait, it's delicious.
It's delicious.
I don't know, I really can't eat this taste, kama shaken people.
No, really.
How about you?
How about it?
Also, there's enough for about 4 people, so please come.
I'm mute.
I'm going mute.
It's delicious.
So, when I started this project, I looked for pictures from my childhood.
I found a lot of them.
I know, right? We all have our mystic-ed scene adults.
Yes?
Yes, yes, yes.
You can't take this grave.
To the white claw grass.
That's great. Maybe this is when they go to plant rice.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mao's mom was really good at making the crown of the white nail grass.
And Mao couldn't do it well at all.
I think she gave it to me and I wear it.
How did you do that, Mao?
But now she can.
Yes, I know.
Yeah, have fun.
I want to go to the rice paddies.
Rice paddies. That was fun, right?
It was fun.
Yeah, it was.
I think I was the bravest and the brightest.
I mean, free and uninhibited.
Oh, this is it.
Ninja.
Ninja house.
I remember the ninja house so well.
It was so much fun!
We were doing this shuriken thing.
And they said it didn't go well.
What?
He was crying so hard.
I got him a souvenir, like a sword.
I still have it at home.
I still have it. I have it at home.
I have it at home.
It's like a Japanese sword, and I'm waving it around, and it's like...
I did this.
That's not bad.
But you have to apologize to the guy at the store.
But I said, "Oh, it's fine, it's fragile," and asked if I could tell him.
They don't have a face.
That's why everyone wanted to buy it.
I'm the one who decided.
Like, "I broke it, so don't buy it anymore.
I know my parents don't want it.
But when we went to Univa...
We went to Universe together.
The one where they let you pick out your own wand.
My brother...
My mom's brother.
My grandma's brother.
They picked you?
Yeah, they picked you.
So you bought it.
I bought it.
What?
I got it.
But you only bought one bottle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then we went to your house.
Yeah, we kind of took turns carrying it.
But we never used it. There was no place to use it.
I don't know why kids want them so bad.
It's true.
It's still sitting there, in my house.
I miss it.
This is my favorite.
I just can't get over how much I love this one.
It's so cute.
It's like drawing local animals.
Like, let's look at the animals and draw a schedule on the guise.
And of course, there were four of us on the front page.
I was in the testimonial group, and I was meeting my sister.
But it's hard to make a decision.
It's a big park.
But it was so hot that day.
We couldn't decide on an animal, and it was hot, and the kids were messing around.
So my mom said, "I don't care what it is, just go ahead and draw it.
I said, "I'll paint a zebra," and we went to the zebras.
But I was going to paint zebras.
And then I remember my mom said, "Whatever, just draw it.
And I was like, "What's the drunkest thing you've ever done?" And I drew a picture of an upperman.
I don't know how old he is.
Maybe two or three years old.
She told me to draw whatever I wanted.
So I converted it in my head into "draw me a picture.
Did you just roll over?
Oh, that's a silver award?
Silver prize.
Why a silver prize?
The people at the shelter over there thought it was a bad idea more than once.
What's that? It says "Zebra" on it, doesn't it?
I'm an upperman, but I drew a lot of zebras on it.
It's so funny.
I was over there, and now I'm kind of surprised that I'm in this situation.
I never thought I'd end up in Tokyo.
I never thought I'd come out with my real name, Seiginji.
Nana-chan, your brother recommended this, right?
Yeah.
I was in a contemplative phase that summer.
He said, "You should try it.
Like, "You should try it.
Lightly.
He told me.
You know, that picture of Mao-chan...
The picture I sent you when I came in... is it on the Internet?
Yeah.
Mao posted it somewhere.
Oh, so that's why.
But you really do smell like a potato.
He's so cute.
Not at all.
That's the Mao-chan I know.
She's so cute now, you'd have to wonder who she is.
Who is she?
Is he cute?
I'm scared
But Mao...
I've seen her on the screen... and she's not the Yo-chan I know.
How long have you been a member, Yochanan?
A year and a half.
And you, Mao?
Well, Mao, it's been two years, and I'm just entering my third year.
So...
So you haven't changed that much.
Since the end of the year on the 2nd.
The 2nd, right?
You were a Jizo, right?
Nagi-chan on the first day, like a Jizo.
Nagi left, right?
Ryo-chan was announced like that, too, like Jizo.
You were the third one.
I had a strange feeling when I saw that.
It's this way.
I was feeling down about school.
I see.
That's right.
I'm glad to hear that.
I don't know what to do.
To be honest, it's a little hard for me to go to school.
But I couldn't stop myself from going to school.
That's when you got a ray of sunshine.
You didn't go to school either, Mom.
She called me up, like she's always getting mad at me.
Yoko, I'd like to come over.
I thought he might have found out about the test I'd been hiding.
I was really surprised.
I've been hearing about how you've been...
So now that I'm here...
I think it's great that we're in different places now.
Yo-chan, you were chosen as the center for the first year, what did you think at first?
I was really surprised.
I'm announcing it now, before I leave the show.
I heard that you haven't even told your mother or sister yet.
I haven't told anyone, really.
But you already told them once.
Yo-chan isn't the center?
I got a kick out of that.
I thought, "What's he talking about?
He didn't tell anyone.
It's partly because she was originally selected for the day group.
I don't know what's going to happen.
I'm really anxious.
I'm sure you're worried.
It's amazing, when you were selected for the first time, you were really nervous the whole time.
But you danced on M STAR during that time.
Somehow...
I thought you were a little...
No, no, no...
She was like a newborn baby.
I thought I was cute.
Positively.
Yeah, it was cute.
But the older students were really nice to me.
They were really nice to me.
The other day, when I got the jacket car, I was the only one in shorts.
And it was outside, so it was really cold.
It was a tough time.
You have a lot of daylight.
Ha-ha-ha.
He warmed me up.
He's so cute!
It's good to have a warm atmosphere.
Yesterday... he choreographed a music video for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everyone was so warm at that time.
I'm really happy to be a member of such a great group.
I see. I'm glad. I'm glad.
I'm feeling the warmth of my seniors and classmates.
I'll probably never graduate.
I see.
That's about as comfortable as it gets.
It's so comfortable.
Uggs.
We're always talking about things that really don't matter.
That's right.
That's why...
I'm not going to tell my mom.
So I want to talk.
You don't have to.
No, but I can't tell you.
You don't have to talk.
So the other day, we got really close.
When Mao-chan came over.
I've been saying that...
I needed some emotional support.
I was so giddy.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I don't know.
Hang in there.
I'll do my best.
We'll both do our best.
Let's do it.
This is
I bought these strawberries at a roadside station Here they are, strawberry pancakes
Strawberry, strawberry, strawberry... You definitely shouldn't... You definitely shouldn't...
I'll eat it, I'll eat it, I'll eat it
One bite and it's gone!
Yes, it's delicious!
Yes, I knew it.
Let's do the last thing we want to do.
Oh, you're gonna do it?
Let's do it.
I'm going to do something that Mao and his friends used to do when they got together.
I'm going to do it today.
Bring it to me.
Okay.
You need the sheet music.
Yes, I want it.
Oh, no, I'll drop it.
There you go.
My guitar.
Your guitar
Fans of Sinatan look at it.
I don't know if I can play it well.
Yoko can do it too.
You can do it!
I don't know, I can't do it.
What?
She can harmonize with me...
So sometimes...
At home.
It's fun to play.
It's fun. We do it all the time.
I play the guitar and they harmonize with me.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I'm having fun.
It's just for fun.
I never thought I'd be able to do it.
No way!
Please look at me warmly.
Here you go.
Please listen to it if you like.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Like your cheeks when you rubbed them.
If your bangs are too cut, they're Yoshi's branches
I wonder why you're depressed when someone says
I don't think so.
It's too dark and sultry for me to take it off.
You're cute.
I can see something.
I'm sorry for looking at myself.
You really got it right.
Even the girl in the picture.
Charming, isn't she?
That's a great shadow.
Unit name.
Shabondeboo
Thank you for watching.
I love this stuff. How long have you been into this?
I don't think any of you would ever fall for it.
I don't think so. I don't think so.
I don't think so. I think you're the cutest girl in the class.
You're the cutest girl in our class.
Look at yourself in the mirror.
Look at yourself in the mirror. You really do fit the bill.
You're just as charming as that girl in the picture.
If you were just like any other girl, I wouldn't like you as much.
You're the only one I'd like because there's no one else.
If you were just like any other girl, I wouldn't like you so much.
I love you because of me, because of you.
We've had a lot going on today.
It was a lot... a lot... a lot... a lot...
For the first time...
I can be a cat.
For the first time together.
I've never done anything like this before.
Hey.
Who's watching?
I don't know.
I think you can see how much I've been acting like a cat.
How long have you been putting out like that, Yochanan?
I was about minus 5 years old today.
You know what I mean?
It was like I was minus 5 years old.
We had a lot of fun!
That's all for the Minato-zaka channel!
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Thank you very much.
Please give us high ratings, channel subscriptions, comments, and views!
LOL!
Lastly, please watch the Nogizaka distribution!
Please watch!
Bye bye!